<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Projects on digitaljoni</title><link>https://digitaljoni.com/projects/</link><description>Recent content in Projects on digitaljoni</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><atom:link href="https://digitaljoni.com/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>PhStocks Tracker</title><link>https://digitaljoni.com/projects/phstocks/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://digitaljoni.com/projects/phstocks/</guid><description>PhStocks Tracker is a mobile app that Philippine stock investors can utilize to watch price changes to their selected stocks. This app is primarily focused on users who use Fundamental Analysis as their investment strategy.
Why I Built The App If you are a busy person (i.e. a full-time employee or a student), you wouldn't have the time to go your stock broker's site daily to check the latest changes to your stocks.</description></item><item><title>Critterpedia</title><link>https://digitaljoni.com/projects/critterpedia/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://digitaljoni.com/projects/critterpedia/</guid><description>The Critterpedia project started as a personal tool when I am playing with the Animal Crossing New Horizons game.
In the game you are tasked to collect different species of fish, insects and sea creatures. You can use these critters to either sell for a price or donate to the museum. Collecting all species of fish and insects would also unlock recipes for golden tools (Golden Fishing rod and Golden Net).</description></item><item><title>NoizArt Project</title><link>https://digitaljoni.com/projects/noizart/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://digitaljoni.com/projects/noizart/</guid><description>The NoizArt project started as an inspiration from Robert Felker (aka The Flutter Artist) where he creates artwork using Dart and Flutter.
In this project it would be a bit different though. Basically most decisions on how the artwork is rendereed are left to the program itself.
It uses the built-in function &amp;ldquo;random&amp;rdquo; to make the decisions it uses a &amp;ldquo;seed&amp;rdquo; value of the current timestamp. Based on the results, the program goes through a decision tree to determine various aspects of the art: canvas color, color theme, what to draw, will there be a foreground, midground and background, and more!</description></item></channel></rss>