<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>digitaljoni</title><link>https://digitaljoni.com/</link><description>Recent content on digitaljoni</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Aug 2020 00:35:37 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://digitaljoni.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Flutter Resources</title><link>https://digitaljoni.com/resources/flutter/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://digitaljoni.com/resources/flutter/</guid><description>Flutter SDK is an open-source mobile app SDK created by Google. Flutter SDK allows you to build an app using a single codebase that can be compiled to both Android and IOS. It is also used to build applications for Google Fuchsia OS.
You write your Flutter applications using a programming language called Dart. Unlike other solutions which uses a bridge, your Dart code gets compiled to machine code. This gives you the advantage of having native performance for your app.</description></item><item><title>PhStocks Tracker</title><link>https://digitaljoni.com/projects/phstocks/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://digitaljoni.com/projects/phstocks/</guid><description>PhStocks Tracker is a mobile app that Philippine stock investors can utilize to watch price changes to their selected stocks. This app is primarily focused on users who use Fundamental Analysis as their investment strategy.
Why I Built The App If you are a busy person (i.e. a full-time employee or a student), you wouldn't have the time to go your stock broker's site daily to check the latest changes to your stocks.</description></item><item><title>Dart Resources</title><link>https://digitaljoni.com/resources/dart/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://digitaljoni.com/resources/dart/</guid><description>Dart is the programming language used on both Flutter and AngularDart. Developed by Google, it aims to enable developers to build complex and high-performing apps. One advantage of using Dart is that you can build your business logic once and use it on both mobile (Flutter) and web (AngularDart) applications. You can even use Dart server-side as well.
Official Dart Site DartPad - a convenient tool to learn Dart syntax (supports Dart’s core libraries) Effective Dart - best practices for building efficient Dart code Dart Cheat Sheet - interactive codelab that demonstrates Dart's features Dart 2 Cheat Sheet - Downloadable 4-page PDF Dart Cheat Sheet and Quick Reference</description></item><item><title>Runes Match 3 - Privacy Policy</title><link>https://digitaljoni.com/app_runes_privacy/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Aug 2020 00:35:37 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://digitaljoni.com/app_runes_privacy/</guid><description>App Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Digitaljoni built the Runes Match 3 app as a Free app. This SERVICE is provided by Digitaljoni at no cost and is intended for use as is.
This page is used to inform visitors regarding my policies with the collection, use, and disclosure of Personal Information if anyone decided to use my Service.
If you choose to use my Service, then you agree to the collection and use of information in relation to this policy.</description></item><item><title>Runes Match 3 - Terms And Conditions</title><link>https://digitaljoni.com/app_runes_terms/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Aug 2020 00:35:37 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://digitaljoni.com/app_runes_terms/</guid><description>Terms &amp;amp; Conditions
By downloading or using the app, these terms will automatically apply to you – you should make sure therefore that you read them carefully before using the app. You’re not allowed to copy, or modify the app, any part of the app, or our trademarks in any way. You’re not allowed to attempt to extract the source code of the app, and you also shouldn’t try to translate the app into other languages, or make derivative versions.</description></item><item><title>How to Apply Gradients To Icons in Flutter</title><link>https://digitaljoni.com/blog/how-to-apply-gradients-to-icons-in-flutter/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Mar 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://digitaljoni.com/blog/how-to-apply-gradients-to-icons-in-flutter/</guid><description>There will be times that a colored icon won't be enough for the UI that you are building in Flutter. How about if we put a gradient color on the icon instead?
The problem is that there is no gradient method on the Icon widget. So we need to use a ShaderMask widget and wrap around the Icon. Here's an example implementation and called it GradientIconWidget:
In order to use this, all you need to do is to pass the icon and gradient that you would like to apply:</description></item><item><title>Git tips: How to Ignore changes to a tracked file</title><link>https://digitaljoni.com/blog/git-tips-how-to-ignore-changes-to-a-tracked-file/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://digitaljoni.com/blog/git-tips-how-to-ignore-changes-to-a-tracked-file/</guid><description>There will be times when you have a file that you would need to edit to test something in your app and you don't want to commit those changes to the repository. Let’s say you have config_dev.dart currently containing settings of your app in a development environment:
const String apiUrl = “localhost:3000/api/articles/“ const bool debugMode = false; Now, for example, you would need to change the URL of the API to point to another local machine or test server within your network.</description></item><item><title>OOP in Dart - DBZ Edition</title><link>https://digitaljoni.com/blog/oop-in-dart-dbz-edition/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://digitaljoni.com/blog/oop-in-dart-dbz-edition/</guid><description>The following slideshow was part of my talk last February 2020 which gives a fun look at object-oriented programming in Dart. I used familiar anime characters to make it easy enough for beginners to understand and to be clear enough to illustrate objects in Dart language.
Slide 1
Imagine you were given the task of creating an RPG set in the Dragonball universe and your task was to develop the Saiyan characters of the game.</description></item><item><title>Hello World</title><link>https://digitaljoni.com/blog/hello-world/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://digitaljoni.com/blog/hello-world/</guid><description>When we start to learn programming we always use the example of printing &amp;ldquo;Hello World&amp;rdquo; in the screen or console. It is a good start for most as it teaches us the basics of how a simple program would work. The text or greeting that we use is also somewhat significant as if our tiny creation is greeting the world and at the same time announcing, hey I am the start of a wonderful adventure for my creator, that there is potential for greatness if this action is continued and improved upon.</description></item><item><title>Privacy Policy</title><link>https://digitaljoni.com/privacy/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Sep 2018 00:35:37 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://digitaljoni.com/privacy/</guid><description>Embedded content from other websites Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.
These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://digitaljoni.com/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://digitaljoni.com/about/</guid><description>Hello! I am JC Sindo, a Senior Flutter Developer from Manila, Philippines.
I started in Flutter Development since 2018 and would love to share with you the wonderful things that I have learned.
Please check out my projects section to see my personal projects.
Other Interests I am interested in anything tech:
Open Source Tech Programming Languages Raspberry Pi Latest Gadgets UI/UX Design I have also delved into the arts and have done:</description></item><item><title>Critterpedia</title><link>https://digitaljoni.com/projects/critterpedia/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://digitaljoni.com/projects/critterpedia/</guid><description>The Critterpedia project started as a personal tool when I am playing with the Animal Crossing New Horizons game.
In the game you are tasked to collect different species of fish, insects and sea creatures. You can use these critters to either sell for a price or donate to the museum. Collecting all species of fish and insects would also unlock recipes for golden tools (Golden Fishing rod and Golden Net).</description></item><item><title>NoizArt Project</title><link>https://digitaljoni.com/projects/noizart/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://digitaljoni.com/projects/noizart/</guid><description>The NoizArt project started as an inspiration from Robert Felker (aka The Flutter Artist) where he creates artwork using Dart and Flutter.
In this project it would be a bit different though. Basically most decisions on how the artwork is rendereed are left to the program itself.
It uses the built-in function &amp;ldquo;random&amp;rdquo; to make the decisions it uses a &amp;ldquo;seed&amp;rdquo; value of the current timestamp. Based on the results, the program goes through a decision tree to determine various aspects of the art: canvas color, color theme, what to draw, will there be a foreground, midground and background, and more!</description></item><item><title>Runes Match 3</title><link>https://digitaljoni.com/projects/runes_match_3/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://digitaljoni.com/projects/runes_match_3/</guid><description>Runes Match 3 is a runes-themed mobile puzzle game where you match 3 tiles in order to remove the tiles and score points per tile.
The game was developed using Flame Engine. It's a 2d Game Engine built on top of Flutter SDK.
Runes match 3 01
Runes match 3 02
Runes match 3 03</description></item></channel></rss>