<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>digitaljoni</title>
    <link>https://digitaljoni.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on digitaljoni</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Sep 2018 00:35:37 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://digitaljoni.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Flutter Resources</title>
      <link>https://digitaljoni.com/resources/flutter/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://digitaljoni.com/resources/flutter/</guid>
      <description>Flutter SDK is an open-source mobile app SDK created by Google. Flutter SDK allows you to build an app using a single codebase that can be compiled to both Android and IOS. It is also used to build applications for Google Fuchsia OS.
You write your Flutter applications using a programming language called Dart. Unlike other solutions which uses a bridge, your Dart code gets compiled to machine code. This gives you the advantage of having native performance for your app.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dart Resources</title>
      <link>https://digitaljoni.com/resources/dart/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://digitaljoni.com/resources/dart/</guid>
      <description>Dart is the programming language used on both Flutter and AngularDart. Developed by Google, it aims to enable developers to build complex and high-performing apps. One advantage of using Dart is that you can build your business logic once and use it on both mobile (Flutter) and web (AngularDart) applications. You can even use Dart server-side as well.
 Official Dart Site DartPad - a convenient tool to learn Dart syntax (supports Dart’s core libraries) Effective Dart - best practices for building efficient Dart code Dart Cheat Sheet - interactive codelab that demonstrates Dart&amp;rsquo;s features Dart 2 Cheat Sheet - Downloadable 4-page PDF Dart Cheat Sheet and Quick Reference  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>https://digitaljoni.com/privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Sep 2018 00:35:37 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://digitaljoni.com/privacy/</guid>
      <description>Embedded content from other websites Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.
These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>